hoppa.com 2015-08-31

# Privacy Policy | hoppa

**1\. SCOPE**

Resorthoppa (UK) Limited, with its registered address at 1st Floor, West Lodge, Station Approach, West Byfleet, Surrey KT14 6NG, company number 04933736 complies with data protection legislation such as the Data Protection Act 1998. This regulates the processing of personal data relating to you and grants you various rights in respect of your personal data.

The aim of this statement is to tell you how we will use any personal data you provide through the hoppa.com website or hoppa app. Please read it carefully before you proceed.

**2\. COLLECTION AND RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We collect a range of personal data from you such as your name, address, date of birth, debit card and credit card details (although we do not store all of your credit, debit card or account details for security reasons). We may also collect information about your usage of the website or app and information from any messages you post to the website or app and e- mails and letters that you send us.

**3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION AND WITH WHOM WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use your personal information in order to provide transportation services and any other services and “extras” available to purchase on our website or app from time to time; to personalize your visits to our website or app; to manage your booking; and to bill you.

We may share your personal data with third parties including the third party principal suppliers of the transport services and/or extras for the purpose of processing and managing your booking.

We may employ the services of a third party to help us in certain areas, such as website hosting. In some cases the third party may receive your information. However, at all times, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information.

We may use aggregated information for the purposes of tracking usage of the web site or app and in order to help us improve our website or app and for research and analysis purposes. We may pass this information to third parties. The aggregate information and statistics will not, however, include details that can be used to identify you.

As part of the booking process, we may make credit searches about you at credit reference agencies. The agencies will record details of any search whether or not your application succeeds. This information may be used by other subscribers for credit decisions. We may use credit scoring methods to assess your offer to make a booking and to verify your identity. Credit searches and other information which is provided to us and/or the credit reference agencies about you and anyone with whom you are linked financially may be used by us if credit decisions are made about you and anyone with whom you are linked financially or other members of your household. This information may be used for debt tracing and the prevention of money laundering as well as the management of our service to you. In addition, we may ask you to provide physical forms of identification and/or we may telephone to confirm your identity.

We may use your information if we are under a legal duty to disclose this; or in order to enforce our website terms of use and any other agreement; and/or to protect the rights of Resorthoppa (UK) Limited.

**4\. DIRECT MARKETING**

We may use your information to contact you for your views on our website, app or services, and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the website, app, services or your booking. If you have consented, we may use your information to let you know about our other products and services that may be of interest to you including services that may be the subject of direct marketing, and we may contact you by telephone, text or e-mail.

If you have consented, we may also share your details with other carefully selected organisations (including those in the travel industry) to enable such organisations to let you know about goods and services which may be of interest to you (by telephone, text and/or email).

**5\. TRANSFER OF YOUR INFORMATION OUTSIDE THE EU**

We may transfer some of your information to countries outside of the EU including but not limited to the Republic of South Africa. Some of these countries may not have equivalent data protection legislation protection the use of your personal information. By submitting your information to the hoppa website or app, you consent to such transfers taking place.

**6\. COOKIES**

**6.1. Use of Cookies on our site**

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are/recognise your computer.

A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number.

When you visit our website we send you a cookie. Cookies may be used in the following ways:

(i) to help us recognise you as a unique visitor (a number) when you return to our website and to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to avoid showing you the same adverts repeatedly;

(ii) to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our site and to help us improve the structure of our website. We cannot identify you personally in this way.

Two types of cookies may be used on this website: session cookies, which are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site, and persistent cookies, which remain in the cookie file of your browser for much longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie).

**6.2.Use of Web Beacons**

Some of our web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes known as clear gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited these pages. Web beacons collect only limited information which include a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. We may also carry web beacons placed by third party advertisers. These beacons do not carry any personally identifiable information and are only used to track the effectiveness of a particular campaign.

**6.3.Third Party Advertising**

We may use a third party to serve advertisements on our site. Cookies may be associated with these advertisements to enable the advertiser to track the number of anonymous users responding to the campaign. We do not have access to or control of cookies placed by third parties.

**6.4. Disabling/Enabling Cookies**

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the interactive features of our site if cookies are disabled.

You can find out how to disable cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

**7\. LINKS**

Our website contains links to other web sites over which we have no control. We are not responsible for privacy policies or practices of other websites to which you choose to link from this site. We encourage to review the privacy policies of those other websites so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.

**8\. SECURITY**

We have implemented reasonable technical and organisational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorised access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, the Internet is an open system and we cannot guarantee that unauthorised third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

**9\. SALE OF THE BUSINESS**

In the event that the hoppa business is transferred or integrated with another business, your details will be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchaser’s adviser and will be passed to the new owners of the business.

**10\. YOUR RIGHT TO ACCESS INFORMATION**

You are entitled to see the information held about you. If you wish to do this, please contact us at Resorthoppa (UK) Limited, 1st Floor, West Lodge, Station Approach, West Byfleet, Surrey KT14 6NG. We may require you to provide verification of your identity and to pay an administration fee (which is currently £10, or local currency equivalent based on the Pound Sterling exchange rate) to provide a copy of the information we hold. Please note that in certain circumstances we may withhold access to your information where we have the right to do so under current data protection legislation.

**11\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

If our privacy policy changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

**12\. CONTACTING US**

If you have any questions about this statement or your personal information, please contact us at Resorthoppa (UK) Limited, 1st Floor, West Lodge, Station Approach, West Byfleet, Surrey KT14 6NG.
